class DummyDb {
  static const List<Map<String, dynamic>> question = [
    {
      "question": "Flutter is ___?",
      "options": [
        "An open-source backend development framework",
        "An open-source UI toolkit",
        "An open-source programming language for cross-platform applications",
        "A DBMS toolkit"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who developed the Flutter Framework and continues to maintain it today?",
      "options": ["Facebook", "Google", "Microsoft", "Oracle"],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many types of widgets are there in Flutter?",
      "options": ["4", "3", "2", "1"],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "When building for iOS, Flutter is restricted to an __ compilation strategy",
      "options": ["JIT(just-in-time)", "Transcompilation", "AOT(ahead-of-time)", "Recompilation"],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "A sequence of asynchronous Flutter events is known as a:",
      "options": [
        "Stream",
        "Series",
        "Current",
        "Flow"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question":
          "Access to a cloud database through Flutter is available through which service?",
      "options": [
        "SQLite",
        "Firebase Database",
        "NOSQL",
        "MYSQL"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What element is used as an identifier for components when programming in Flutter?",
      "options": ["Widgets", "Elements", "Keys", "Series"],
      "answerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of test can examine your code as a complete system?",
      "options": [
        "Integration tests",
        "Unit tests",
        "Widget tests",
        "All of the above"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question":
          "What command would you use to compile your Flutter app in release mode?",
      "options": ["Flutter --release", "Flutter run --release", "Flutter run release", "Flutter build --release"],
      "answerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which function will return the widgets attached to the screen as a root of the widget tree to be rendered on screen?",
      "options": [
        "runApp()",
        "main()",
        "container()",
        "root()"
      ],
      "answerIndex": 0
    }
  ];
}
